Guide to the Rosalinda Guillén and Joseph Moore Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Rosalinda Guillén and Joseph Moore Papers [Guía A Los Archivos De Rosalinda Guillén Y Joseph Moore], 1982-2011; 5799-001; 20.54 cubic feet [Cantidad: 20.54 Pies Cúbicos] 19 boxes [19 cajas]
  - Farm Labor Contractor, Part 2 of 2 [Contratista de Labor Agrícola, Parte 2 de 2], 1992-2000 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Organization of Los Angeles Workers (OLAW) Presentations [Organización de Trabajadores de Los Angeles (OLAW) Presentaciones], 2000-2003 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Latino Vote, Reports and Trends [Voto Latinoamericano, Informes y Tendencias], 1995-2001 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Latino Election Handbook [Manual de Elección Latinoamericana], 2000-2002 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance [Alianza Laboral Norteamericano del Pacífico Asiático], 2000 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Labor Campaign Plan, South Bay AFL-CIO Labor Council [Plan de Campaña de Trabajo, Bahía del Sur Afl-Cio Consejo de Trabajo], 2000 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - California Assembly Democrats [Asamblea de Demócratas de California], 2000-2002 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Latino Committee, Los Angeles Democratic National Convention [Comité Latino, Convención Nacional Demócrata en Los Angeles], 2000 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - California Latino Politics [Política Latina de California], 2000-2002 (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Presidential Policies, Powerpoint Printouts [Políticas Presidenciales, Powerpoint Listado], 2003 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Rainbow Coalition 2003 [Coalición Rainbow 2003], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Rainbow Coalition 2004 [Coalición Rainbow 2004] (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Rainbow Coalition Two Year Plan [Coalición Rainbow Plan de Dos Años], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Subcontracted Work Initiative Strategy Forum [Foro de Estrategia de Iniciativa de Trabajo Subcontratado], 2001 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - The 1999 Imperial Valley Asparagus Harvest [La Cosecha de Espárrago de Valle Imperial 1999] (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Immigration Studies [Estudios de Inmigración], 1993-1999 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - H2A "Guest Workers" Legislation, Part 1 of 4 [H2A Legislación "De Trabajadores Inmigrantes," Parte 1 de 4], 1998 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - H2A "Guest Workers" Legislation, Part 2 of 4 [H2A Legislación "De Trabajadores Inmigrantes," Parte 2 de 4], 1999 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - H2A "Guest Workers" Legislation, Part 3 of 4 [H2A Legislación "De Trabajadores Inmigrantes," Parte 3 de 4], 1999 (Box-folder 9/20)
  - H2A "Guest Workers" Legislation, Part 4 of 4 [H2A Legislación "De Trabajadores Inmigrantes," Parte 4 de 4], 1999 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Census 2000, Part 1 of 3 [Censo 2000, Parte 1 de 3] (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Census 2000, Part 2 of 3 [Censo 2000, Parte 2 de 3] (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Census 2000, Part 3 of 3 [Censo 2000, Parte 3 de 3] (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Texas-Mexico Water Dispute [Controversias por el Agua Entre Texas y México.], 2002 (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Metropolitan Water District (MWD)/ Palo Verde Irrigation District [Distrito Metropolitano del Agua (MWD) / Palo Verde Distrito de Irrigación], 2001 (Box-folder 9/26)
  - Wetlands Land Retirement [Retiro de las Tierras Pantanosas], 2002 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - The National Association of Latino Elected and Appointed Officials Educational Fund (NALEO)/ Metropolitan Water District (MWD), Policy Institute on Water Management for Local Latino Elected Officials [Asociación Nacional de Latinos Electos y Fondo Educativo de la Asociación Nacional de Funcionarios Latinos, Electos y Designados (NALEO, por Sus Siglas en Ingles) / Departamento de Agua (MWD), Instituto de Política sobre Gestión del Agua para Latinos Electos y Nombrados], 2001 (Box-folder 9/28)
  - CALFED, Environmental Justice Working Group [CALFED, Grupo de Trabajo de Justicia Ambiental], 2001 (Box-folder 9/29)
  - Wetbacks [Mojado], 1999 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - UFW Water Policy [UFW Política del Agua], 2001 (Box-folder 9/31)
  - Metropolitan Water District (MWD), Ron Gastelum [Distrito Metropolitano del Agua (MWD), Ron Gastelum], 2001 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Employment Development Department (EDD)/H-2A Temporary Alien Agricultural Worker Program [Departamento del Desarollo del Empleo (EDD)/H-2A Programa del Trabajadores Agrícolas Temporales Extranjeros], 2002-2002 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Hoffman Plastic Compounds v. National Labor Relations Board [Compuestos de Plástico de Hoffman, Inc V. Junta Nacional de Relaciones Laborales], 2002 (Box-folder 9/34)
  - Immigration Issues 2001 [Tema de Inmigración 2001] (Box-folder 9/35)
  - H2A Issues 2002 [H2A Cuestiónes 2002], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 9/36)
  - Migrant Farm Labor Policy [Política Laboral del Inmigrante Campesino], 2002 (Box-folder 9/37)
  - The 2002 Central Valley Raisin Harvest [2002 Cosecha de Pasas del Valle Central] (Box-folder 9/38)
  - H2A Harry Singh & Sons [H2A Harry Singh y Hijos], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 9/39)
  - National Farm Worker Advocacy Conference [Conferencia Nacional de Propugnación de los Trabajadores Agrícolas], 2002 (Box-folder 9/40)
  - National Council of La Raza (NCLR) National Migrant Farmworker Summit, New Mexico [Consejo Nacional de La Raza, Cumbre Nacional de Trabajadores Agrícolas], 2001 (Box-folder 9/41)
  - (Box-folder 10)
    Box 10, which contained sensitive finanical records, was returned to the donor after appraisal and review. [Notas Generales: Caja 10, Contiene Registros Financieros Privados, que Fueron Devueltos al Donante Después de su Apreciación y Revisión]
  - Capital Press Agriculture Weekly [Capital De Prensa Semanal De La Agricultura], January 21, 2005-December 16, 2005 (Box-folder 11a/1)
  - Capital Press Agriculture Weekly [Capital De Prensa Semanal De La Agricultura], May 5, 2006-December 29, 2006 (Box-folder 11a/2)
  - Whatcom Independent [Whatcome Independiente], June 1st, 2006-October 4, 2006 (Box-folder 11b/1)
  - Bellingham Herald [El Heraldo de Bellingham], August 7, 2005-October 15, 2006 (Box-folder 11b/2)
  - Miscellaneous Publications & Press Clippings: The AS Review, The Associated Press Special Report, Cascadia Weekly, Co-op Community News, The Foothills Gazette, The Northern Light, New York Times, The Sacramento Bee, Seattle Times, Skagit Valley Herald, So [Publicaciones Mixtas y Recortes De Prensa: Revista AS Review, Informe Especial de Associated Press, Cascadia Weekly, Co-Op Noticias de la Comunidad, Periódico Foothills Gazette, Periódico Northern Light, Periódico New York Times, Periódico The Sacramento Bee, Periódico Seattle Times, El Heraldo de Skagit Valley], December 18 ,1997-December 2006 (Box-folder 11b/3)
  - Indigenous Women's Network, Strengthening the Circle [Red de Mujeres Indîgenas, Fortalecimiento del Círculo], May 2004 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Indigenous Women's Network, Strengthening the Circle [Red de Mujeres Indîgenas, Fortalcimiento del Círculo], November 2004 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Indigenous Women's Network [Red de Mujeres Indîgenas], May 2004 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - State of the Possible Northwest Social Forum 2004 [Estado de Lo Posible, Foro Social de Noroeste 2004], April 2004 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Food Lab Steering Committee [Comité Directivo del Laboratorio de Alimentos], January 2004-February 2004 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Food Lab [Laboratorio de Alimentos], May 2004-December 2005 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Food Lab-Food 4 Health Team [Laboratorio de Alimentos 4 Equipo de Salúd], November 2005-February 2006 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Food Lab Team Members [Miembros del Equipo del Laboratorio de Alimentos], April 2005 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Foundation Workshop [Taller de Fundación], June 2004 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Sustainable Food Laboratory Planning [Planificación del Laboratorio de Alimentos Sustenables], June 2004 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Learning Journeys- Brazil [Estudio de Viajes- Brasil], August 2004-October 2004 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Sustainable Food Laboratory [Laboratorio de Alimentos Sustenables], August 2004-November 2004 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - (Sustainable Food Laboratory) [Laboratorio de Alimentos Sustenables], January 2003-May 2005 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Sustainable Food Laboratory Planning [Planeación del Laboratorio de Alimentos Sustenables], April 2004 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Food and Society Conference- Panel Labor, Social Justice and Food System [Conferencia de Alimentos y Sociedad- Grupo de Trabaho, La Justicia Social y del Sistema Alimenticio], January 2004-May 2004 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Food Lab- Costa Rica [Laboratorio de Alimentos- Costa Rica], November 2005 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Be a Local Hero Buy Locally Grown W.K. Kellogg [Sea Un Héroe Local, Compre la Cosecha Local W.K. Kellogg], April 2005 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Scenario Retreat [Marcha Atrás De Argumento], August 2004-November 2004 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Learning Journey [Estudio de Viaje], July 2004-September 2004 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Programa de Crédito Fundiario, August 2004-September 2004 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - Sustainability Report [Informe de Sustentabilidad], 2001 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - Sustainable Food Laboratory [Laboratorio de Alimentos Sustenables], April 2005 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - Sustainable Food Laboratory [Laboratorio de Alimentos Sustenables], June 2004-August 2004 (Box-folder 12/23)
  - Framing Team- Sustainable Food Production[Formación De Equipo - Producción Sustentable De Alimentos], March 2005-October 2005 (Box-folder 12/24)
  - Framing Team- Sustainable Food Laboratory [Formación de Equipo – Laboratorio Sustentable de Alimentos], November 2004 (Box-folder 12/25)
  - (Europeans and Sustainable Food Qualitative Study) [Europeos Y Estudio Sostenible Cualitativo De Alimentos], c. 2000's (Box-folder 12/26)
  - Salzburg Seminar [Seminario del Salzburg], April 2005 (Box-folder 12/27)
  - Washington Free Trade Agreement [Tratado de Libre Comercio del Estado de Washington], June 2000-December 2003 (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Union Tactics Matter [Materia De Táctica De Unión], July 1995 (Box-folder 12/29)
  - Newspaper/Newsletter Originals: Bellingham Herald, Cascadia Weekly, Co-op Community News, Free Church Unitarian Newsletter, Foothills Gazette, Labor Center News, The Northern Light, El Periodico, Seeds Quarterly, Skagit Valley Herald, Tacoma Weekly, Tribu [Periódicos/Boletínes Informativos Originales: Bellingham Herald, Cascadia Weekly, Co-Op Community News, Free Church Unitarian Newsletter, Foothills Gazette, Labor Center News, The Northern Light, El Periódico, Seeds Quarterly, Skagit Valley Herald, Tacoma Weekly, Tribu], January 18, 2004-August 1, 2011 (Box-folder 13a/1)
  - Newspaper, Newsletter, and Magazine Originals: Bellingham Herald, Intelligence Report, New York Times, Real Change, Seattle Times, Whatcom Independent [Periódicos, Boletín De Noticias, y Revistas Originales: Bellingham Herald, Intelligence Report, New York Times, Real Change, Seattle Times, Whatcom Independent.], July 23, 2007-December 11, 2007 (Box-folder 13a/2)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Originals: Bellingham Herald, Co-op Community News, Latina Magazine, Mother Jones, New York Times, Seattle Post-Intelligencer, Southern Poverty Law Center Report, Whatcom Independent [Periódicos yRevistas Originales: Bellingham Herald, Co-Op Community News, Latina Magazine, Mother Jones, New York Times, Seattle Post-Intelligencer, Southern Poverty Law Center Report, Whatcom Independent], May 2, 2006-May 6, 2007 (Box-folder 13a/3)
  - Misc. Newspaper/Newsletter Originals [Diversos Periódicos/Boletínes Informativos], 1996-2005 (Box-folder 13a/4)
  - Newspaper Originals, Bellingham Herald, Capital Press, Co-op Community News, La Raza Noroeste, New York Times, Seattle Times, Whatcom Independent [Periódicos Originales: Bellingham Herald, Capital Press, Co-Op Community News, La Raza Noroeste, New York Times, Seattle Times, Whatcom Independent], September 17, 2006-September 02, 2007 (Box-folder 13b/1)
  - Newspaper & Program Originals: Terraviva, 5o Acampamento Intercontinental da Juventude, Forum Social Mundial [Periódicos y Programas Originales: Terra Viva, 5o Acampamento Intercontinental de la Juventud, El Foro Social Mundial], January 24-31, 2005 (Box-folder 13b/2)
  - La Campesina 88.3 FM Latino Promotional Partnership [Asociación Promocional Latin], c. 2001-2001 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Pocket Roster and Government Guide; Other UFW Information Pamphlets [Listado de Bolsillo y Guía de Gobierno; Otra Información UFW Folletos], 2000-2002 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Acuerdo de Convenio Colectivo (Collective Bargaining Agreement) between UFW and Employers, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Constitution of the United Farm Workers of America AFL-CIO Unión de Campesinos [Constitución de Los Labradores Unidos de América AFL - CIO Unión de Campesinos.], 1992-1996 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - U.S. Congress Directory [Directorio de Congreso Estadosunidense], 2002-2002 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - ACTA De la Décimo-Segunda (Tercera, Cuarta) Convención Constitucional de la Unión de Campesinos de América, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Newspaper Clips of Rival UFW Groups [Recortes de Periódico de Grupos Rivales UFW], 1997-1997 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Hartsel and Olivieri Certified Short Hand Reporters, Deposition of Sergio Soto [Hartsel y Olivieri Certificó a Reporteros de Taquigrafía, Deposición de Sergio Soto], 1998-1998 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Teamsters Election, Stemilt Washington Fruit [Elección de Camioneros, Fruta de Stemilt en Washington], 1997-1997 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Administración Laboral Agrícola Cultivando La Productividad del Personal (The Agricultural Labor Management Cultivating Personnel Productivity), 1991-1991 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Berry Farm Informationals [Información sobre la Granja de Berry], 1994-1997 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Supervisor Training Material [Material Didáctico de Supervisores], 1996-1997 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - VCNM Berry Farms [VCNW Granjas de Berry], 1997-1997 (Box-folder 14/13)
  - Manual Para Junta [Joint Manuals], c.2000-c.2000 (Box-folder 14/14)
  - Acuerdo de Convenio Colectivo Entre UFW y La Granja de Berry Swanton [Collective Bargaining Agreement between UFW and Swanton Berry Farms], 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - Policies and Procedures of the UFW [Polîtica y Procedimientos de UFW], 1998-1998 (Box-folder 14/16)
  - Farm Worker Movement Survey Results and Workshop [Resultados del Estudio del Movimiento de los Trabajadores Agrícolas y del Taller], 1998-1998 (Box-folder 14/17)
  - Unions: Target 2000, High Performance Management [Sindicatos: Meta 2000, Dirección de Gran Rendimiento], 1995-1995 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - Brochures and Maps [Folletos y Mapas], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 15/1)
  - FETAG-RS, A Forca da Mobilizacao Consolidada no Tempo, "The Strength of the Consolidated Mobilization in Time" Jornal da Confederacao Nacional dos Trabalhadores na Agricultura, "Journal of the National Confederation of Workers in Agriculture" Jornal da FE ["Diario de la Confederación Nacional de Trabajadores en Agricultura" Jornal Da Fe], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Forum Social Mundial Um Outro Mundo e Possivel, "World Social Forum: Another World is Possible", and Miscellaneous Papers ["Foro Social Mundial: Otro Mundo es Posible", y Papeles Diversos], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Organizacion Internacional de Mujeres Pro Derechos Humanos (MADRE), "An International Women's Human Rights Organization" and other Human Rights Material, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Northwest Social Forum (NWSF) [Foro Social de Noroeste], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - Northwest Social Forum (NWSF), Program Work Group, Part 1 of 3 [Foro Social de Noroeste, Programa de Grupo de Trabajo, Parte 1 de 3], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Northwest Social Forum (NWSF), Program Work Group, Part 2 of 3 [Foro Social de Noroeste, Programa de Grupo de Trabajo, Parte 2 de 3], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Northwest Social Forum (NWSF), Program Work Group, Part 3 of 3 [Foro Social de Noroeste, Programa de Grupo de Trabajo, Parte 3 de 3], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Northwest Social Forum (NWSF) "Strengthening the Social Change Networks in the Northwest" [Foro Social de Noroeste "Fortalecimiento de las Redes de Cambio Social en el Noroeste"], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Northwest Social Forum, Charter of Principles [Foro Social de Noroeste, Carta de Principios], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Northwest Social Forum Retreat,Committee Meetings [Retiro del Foro Social del Noroeste, Reuniónes de Comité], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Northwest Social Forum, Whatcom County [Foro Social de Noroeste, Condado de Whatcom], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Northwest Social Forum, Asian Pacific American Community Summit [Foro Social de Noroeste, Cumbre de Comunidad Asiática Pacífica Americana], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/13)
  - Northwest Social Forum, Food Justice Track and Round Table Discussion [Foro Social de Noroeste, Pista de Justicia de Alimentos y Discusión de Mesa Redonda], 2003-2004 (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Northwest Social Forum, Event Coordinator [Foro Social de Noroeste, Coordinador del Evento], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - Northwest Social Forum, Retreat at Dumas Bay Center [Foro Social de Noroeste, Retiro en Dumas Bay Center], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/16)
  - Northwest Social Forum, Fundraising [Foro Social de Noroeste, Recaudación de Fondos], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - Northwest Social Forum, Retreat Invitations [Foro Social de Noroeste, Invitaciónes al Retiro], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/18)
  - Northwest Social Forum, Retreat, Planning Committee Report [Foro Social de Noroeste, Retiro, Informe del Comité Directivo], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/19)
  - Northwest Social Forum, Retreat, Follow Up [Foro Social de Noroeste, Retiro, Seguimiento], 2004-2004 (Box-folder 15/20)
  - Vancouver Community Social Forum, Black Mesa [Foro Social de la Comunidad de Vancouver, Black Mesa (Una Meseta en el Noreste de Arizona, Hogar de Muchos de los Navajos. Los Hopi Viven en Extensiones del Sur)], 2003-2004 (Box-folder 15/21)
  - State of the Possible, The Positive Futures Network [El Estado de Lo Posible, La Red de Futuro Positivo], 2000-2004 (Box-folder 15/22)
  - Agricultural Labor Relations Board (ALRB) [Consejo de Relaciones Laborales Agrícola (ALRB)], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Assembly Bill No. 2596 Wesson [Cuenta de Asamblea el No. 2596 Wesson], 2002-2002 (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Fair Farm Worker Legislation and Governor Gray Davis [Legislación Justa de Campesinos y el Gobernador Gray Davis], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Senate Bill No. 1156 Burton [Cuenta De Senado No. 1156 Burton], 2002-2002 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Senate Bill No. 1736 Burton [Cuenta De Senado No. 1736 Burton], 2002-2002 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Governor Gray Davis and California Bills [Gobernador Gray Davis y Cuentas de California], 2000-2002 (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Agricultural Labor Relations Board (ALRB) Certification and Decertification List [Consejo de Relaciones Laborales Agrícolas (ALRB) Certificación y Lista de Decertificación], 2002-2002 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Agricultural Labor Relations Board (ALRB) Negotiations [Consejo de Relaciones Laborales Agrícolas (ALRB) Negociaciones], 2002-2002 (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Governor Gray Davis Economic Summit [Gobernador Gray Davis Cumbre Económica], 2001-2001 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Definicion Y Deberes De Los Comites, Definition and Duties of Committees, 1996-1996 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Convocation [Convocatoria], 1999-2002 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - United Farm Workers of America Civic Action Calendar [Calendario de Acción Cívico de los Campesinos Unidos de América], 2000-2000 (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Latino Vote, Civic Participation Training [Voto Latino, Entrenamiento de Participación Cívica], 2001-2001 (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Cesar Chavez Rose Planting Ceremony for Senate Bill 1736 [Cesar Chavez Ceremonia de Plantación de Rosas por Ley del Senado 1736], 2002-2002 (Box-folder 16/14)
  - UFW Secretaries of Civic Action Presentations on Latino Census, Voting, Education [UFW Los Secretarios de Acción Cívica Presentaciones sobre el Censo Latinoamericano, Votación, Educación], 1998-2000 (Box-folder 16/15)
  - UFW Secretaries of Civic Action Worker Convocation [UFW Secretarios de Acción Cívica Convocatoria de Trabajadores], 1999-2000 (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Senate Bill 996 Worker's Compensation Hearing, Sacramento [Proyecto de Ley del Senado 996 Audiencia de Compensación de los Trabajadores, Sacremento], 2000-2000 (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Video Tapes, Audiocasettes [Cintas de Video, Casetes de Audio], c. 1990-c. 2005 (Box-folder 17)
  - Partido dos Trabalhadores (PT), Workers' Party Brazil, Flag Movimento dos Trabalhadores Sem Terra (MST), Landless Workers' Movement, Flag Grassroots Global Justice, World Social Forum, Flag Federação dos Trabalhadores na Agricultura no Rio Grande do Sul (Box-folder Bag)
    These items were dispersed among other boxes, per CMC. [SEK 5/29/2014]
- Rosalinda Guillén and Joseph Moore papers, 1990s; 5799-002; 1 Oversize Folder
  Bandana from the United Farm Workers of Washington's Chateau St. Michel Campaign. Features an image of a wine Chateau St. Michel wine bottle and a list of related brands to boycott such as Columbia Crest, Villa Mt. Eden, Conn Creek, V.M. WItbye, Farron Ridge.
  No restrictions on access.
  Rosalinda Guillén